northpark.edu 2013-12-29

# Privacy Policy - North Park University - Christian, Urban, Multicultural

## Information We Collect

North Park University routinely collects information from website visitors when they respond to a survey or fill out a form. Visitors should understand that they are voluntarily submitting this information and releasing it to North Park University for specific purposes expressed in this policy.

When registering on the University’s website, applying for admission to the University or registering for classes or other University services visitors may be asked to enter their:

  * Name 
  * Date of Birth 
  * Email Address 
  * Mailing Address 
  * Phone Number

Visitors may be required to submit credit card information under these circumstances:

  * Registering for classes, seminars, or workshops 
  * Making payments for housing, tuition, or fees as an admitted student 
  * Purchasing tickets for University-sponsored events 
  * Purchasing books and University merchandise online

Applying to the University as a student will require individuals to submit their Social Security Number if applicable.

## Usage of Collected Information

### Processing Transactions

Visitor information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. 

### Sending Periodic Email Messages

Visitors who provide an email address may be added to one or more mailing lists maintained by the University. These lists are used for recruiting students, promoting events, and providing news and information to interested parties. Recipients of email messages from University mailing lists may unsubscribe from receiving future emails at any time. The University will include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email message.

## Protecting Collected Information

North Park University maintains a variety of security measures to safeguard personal information.

The University maintains a secure server. All supplied sensitive and credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, private information (credit cards, Social Security Numbers, financial information, etc.) will not be stored on University servers.

## Use of Cookies

Cookies are small files that a site transfers to a visitor’s computer hard drive through the web browser if the visitor allows. Cookies enable the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize the visitor’s browser and capture and remember certain information.

North Park University uses cookies to understand and save visitor preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

## Disclosure of Information to Outside Parties

North Park University does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer personal information collected online in the course of University services and operation to outside parties, businesses, or organizations. This does not include trusted third parties contracted to assist website operations, servicing web visitors or other business. However, the University will require all such third-parties to adhere to reasonable standards for privacy and protection of personal information. The University may also release personal information when such release is deemed appropriate to comply with the law, enforce site policies, or protect rights, property, or safety of the University, its students, faculty and staff or others. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information from other websites or sources that are not published online.

## Visitor Consent

By using the North Park University website, visitors give their consent to this privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

North Park University will post any and all changes to its Privacy Policy on this page. This policy was last modified on June 11, 2009.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us by [email](http://www.northpark.edu/About/Contact-North-Park/Email-North-Park) or by phone at (773) 244-5215.
